<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Finally. It's nice to speak to someone who can help me. I'm $Character_4$, nice to meet you, etcetera. Be a dear and arrange me someplace to stay will you? My research has been stalled for long enough.][UnlockBuildingID:16][Name:Introduction]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:$Name$. I hope you're well? Good.][Default][Name:1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh, hello. I guess I have a moment. My latest experiment hasn't proven fruitful.][Default][Name:2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Text:For me? Oh no, you shouldn't have!][Name:Gift]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Text:You got this for me? I... thank you. really, this will be invaluable to my research.][Name:Collection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hey, $Name$, what do you need?][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Are you sure? I guess I can join you for an adventure today.][Name:JoinPartyYes]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Sorry... I've got things to do today. Maybe later?][Name:JoinPartyNo]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Yes I will marry you!][Name:MarriageYes]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh... I'm sorry but... No.][Name:MarriageNo]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I hate weather like this. It just serves to delay my research.][Weather:Raining][Name:Raining|1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hm. I'm thinking I might take a walk. I despise the rain, but there are several species of flowers I'm interested in that only bloom in the rain.][Weather:Raining][Name:Raining|2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I love my brother, but he can be so frustratingly vain sometimes. I was trying to tell him about my latest magical discovery and do you know what he said to me afterwards?
"Do you think this new pin goes with my robes."
I swear, he doesn't listen to a word I say.][Villager:3][Name:Emmanuel_1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>13</Key>
      <Value>[Text:$Name$, you know $Character_6$ right? Do you have any idea why she asked me to arm wrestle the other day?
I didn't know what to say, so I just stood there, staring at her until she left.][Villager:6][Name:Daria_1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>14</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I tried to talk with $Character_17$ the other day but she just blew me off. She said she had no time for me! Can you believe that!][Villager:17][Name:Griselda_1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>15</Key>
      <Value>[Text:You know, $Character_2$ is a lot more knowledgeable than he looks, once you get him to stop babbling and talk straight.][Villager:2][Name:Michael_1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>16</Key>
      <Value>[Text:$Character_11$ said she was going to try to get a book for me, but it hasn't arrived yet. Do you think it's too soon to ask her about it?][Villager:11][Name:Isabelle_1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>17</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I sometimes get the feeling that some of the others are afraid of me. They hurry away if they see me coming, and won't meet me eyes.][Name:Scared_Of_Me]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
