<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Greetings. I am a traveler of sorts, searching the lands for curios and curiosities. $Actor_22$ is my name and I would entreat your aid.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:IntroYes][Text:Oh. How interesting. In that case, you should speak with $2$, he and his husband make excellent weapons.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:IntroNo][Text:Oh, that's a shame]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Name:IntroMaybe][Text:What does that even mean?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Insects][Text:I was speaking to the insects in the forest last night. They didn't have anything interesting to say, but they're good listeners.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Strange People][Text:I've been alone for quite some time you know. Being around people agian is... strange, but exhilarating. You are all so very strange.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:Oh, that's surprising. Thank you.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Is that for me? Oh! Thank you! It's just what I've been looking for! How did you know?][Name:Collection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hello, what can I do for you?][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_10_Start][Text:I have spent years studying ancient texts that pre-date the war. They were scattered, hard to find and difficult to understand. I would build an $WorldObject_30$ here to better record our history.
This land has a sense of importance about it and I feel that this task is of the utmost importance. Should warfare come again, greater than the last, we must prepare to preserve our knowledge for the future.][UnlockObjectID:30]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Sorry,I'm very busy today. Maybe in a few days I can go with you again.][Name:JoinPartyNo]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Yes I will marry you!][Name:MarriageYes]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh... I'm sorry but. No.][Name:MarriageNo]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
