<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Text:You lost or something? Ain't no villages around these parts for miles.
	  ...
	  You're what now? Building a town out here? Well ain't that something. I've always thought a town could do well for itself out here. The name's $^$, once upon a time I was a ship's captain but now I've retired. ][Name:Introduction]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Out for some adventure are you? Don't get into too much trouble.][Default][Name:1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I'm glad to see you out and about, does my old heart good to see there's still firecrackers like you out in the world.][Default][Name:2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Text:For me? Well, I didn't ask for nothing but I'm not one to refuse any hospitality.][Name:Gift]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hey.][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Text:What in blazes are you doing out in weather like this? Go home and get dry! Whatever you're up to will be there tomorrow!][Weather:Raining][Name:Raining|1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Once upon a time, the rain didn't bother me. After a lifetime at sea though, I think I've earned myself the right to stay dry by a comfy fire.][Weather:Raining][Name:Raining|2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Text:... hm? Oh, hello dear. I was lost in my thoughts. It's alovely day out, isn't it? My husband and I used to go out for walks on days like this.][Weather:Snowing][Name:Snowing|1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Text:You know... now that I've settled in, I was thinking. This town could really use an $Building_24$. It's been so long since I've taught anyone. My Jesse would sit at my knees and listen to my tell him the names of all the plants and herbs...
If you could build me such a place, that would make an old woman very happy.][ShopTargetID:2][UnlockItemID:137][Once][Default][Priority:50][Name:Apothecary_Request]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I was wondering if you could help me. A few days ago, a monster crept into my house and scared the daylights out of me! The worst part though, was that the little thief stole my book of recipes and made off towards the Forest Temple to the North!
	  You look like someone equipped to deal with monsters, would it be too much trouble to ask you to go and get it for me? I've had that book for years, and all of my most important recipes are in it.
	  Thank you so much!
	  It ran North, to the Forest Temple. You'll need to make an offering at the door to get it open, so make sure you find a $Item_162$. I've got some $Item_142$ that I've been saving, but you'll need it as well, so here. Good luck, and be careful!][Name:Task_3_Start][ItemID:142]</Value>
    </Item>
	<Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Text:That's it! Thank you so much!][Name:Task_3_End]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
