<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh hello, you must be the welcome commitee. Imust say I was hoping the town my sister had decided to settle down in would have a bit more glamor but she never was one to worry about that.
Could you fix me up a place to live please? I'm afraid that I'm stuck here with you all forthe forseeable future.][UnlockBuildingID:15][Name:Introduction]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hi $Name$. You know, seeing you running around is one of the few bright bright spots of this place. You're so driven, it's inspiring.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I'm not used to living on the outskirts like this. There's dirt everywhere. Do you have any idea how often I have to wash my robes to keep them clean? How do you handle it?][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Text:For me? Oh no, you shouldn't have!][Name:Gift]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Text:How did you get this out here? I thought I would have needed to take a trip out of town to get this! Thank you so much!][Name:Collection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hey, $Name$, what do you need?][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Are you sure? I guess I can join you for an adventure today.][Name:JoinPartyYes]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Sorry... I've got things to do today. Maybe later?][Name:JoinPartyNo]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Yes I will marry you!][Name:MarriageYes]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh... I'm sorry but... No.][Name:MarriageNo]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Text:This town has it's quaint charm but... I miss the city. I can't wait until $Character_4$ and I have finished our business here.][Name:Dialogue|3]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I didn't think I'd see you today. I always jump at the opportunity to do nothing on rainy days. I guess you've got more on your plate than I do though, hm?][Weather:Raining][Name:Raining|1]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
