<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Who's there?!
Oh, you don't look threatening. Any chance you came from a place called $Town$? I'm supposed to be heading there but I appear to have gotten turned around.
You do? Great. The name's Ulm, and it'll be a pleasure to meet you once you do me a small favor.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:BAM][Text:Every once in a while, some beastie thinks I look like a snack. A quick whack to the head with a stone pestle will sort out most things.
BAM!
Hehe...][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Mortar and Pestle][Text:I've found that there's not much in life that can't be solved with a sturdy mortar and pestle.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Name:ShopOpen][Text:Yes, what is it?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:Wow! Thanks!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hey.][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_Start][Text: I've been wandering through these woods all day and I'm just too tired to move another foot. I think $Item_163$ grows around here, doesn't it? That should give me the strength to continue for now.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_End][Text:Is that $Item_163$ I smell?
Knew I could count on you.
...
Ah! That hits the spot. Now then, where was that town you said? Great, I'll see you there, and then we can talk business!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_2_Start][Text:You call this a town? More like a sad clump of buildings if you ask me...
	  Lucky for you, I am an expert Apothecary. You build me a nice little home to call my own, and I'll see to it that the merchants have more than enough potions and unguents to keep them coming.][UnlockObjectID:18]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
