<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Again, I thank you for your aid. It would appear that the Spirits took my previous offerings and, as a result, left me trapped. Perhaps we might help one another?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:IntroYes][Text:Oh. How interesting. In that case, you should speak with $2$, he and his husband make excellent weapons.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:IntroNo][Text:Oh, that's a shame]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Name:IntroMaybe][Text:What does that even mean?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Insects][Text:I was speaking to the insects in the forest last night. They didn't have anything interesting to say, but they're good listeners.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Strange People][Text:I've been alone for quite some time you know. Being around people agian is... strange, but exhilarating. You are all so very strange.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:Oh, that's surprising. Thank you.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Collection][Text:Is that for me? Oh! Thank you! It's just what I've been looking for! How did you know?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Selection][Text:You have returned. What do you require of me?][Selection:VillageTalk]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_10_Start][Text:I have been contemplating my next move and I think that this village you shall make a fine home for me to continue my research, at least for now.
I am... a scholar of sorts, seeking out relics of the past and present. I wish to record the various items and resources found int his land.
 You are a Builder, yes? As such, your duties will have you scouring the land for your materials. I ask only that you bring them to me as well, so that I may research them. Herbs, Potions, Relics from the past as well as any tomes you might find.
 I will make it worth your while to furnish my $WorldObject_30$.][UnlockObjectID:30]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Sorry,I'm very busy today. Maybe in a few days I can go with you again.][Name:JoinPartyNo]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Yes I will marry you!][Name:MarriageYes]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh... I'm sorry but. No.][Name:MarriageNo]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
