<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Well hello there! The name's $Actor_11$ and I heard about this little village you've started here. Now, I'm a man who knows opportunity when he smells it and let me tell you, that is what this place smells like.
]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Money in the air][Text:I love days like this. The sun is shining, the skies are clear, and you can just smell money in the air.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:2][Text:I used to have a shop down in Westgate a few years back. Sold it to a nice man before I moved on myself. I wonder how he's doing?][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Name:ShopOpen][Text:Oh, hello $Name$, What can I do for you?][Selection:Shop]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:Thank you!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Selection][Text:Well now, what can I do for you?][Selection:VillageTalk]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Raining|1][Text:It's good to see you out and about in this weather. Can I interest you in anything? Rain isn't very good for business.][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Raining|2][Text:I've heard tell that the woods here are full of nature spirits. Apparently some of them can even be seen playing in the rain at times. CAn't say I've manged to catch sight of one myself though.][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_12_Start][Text:I'm here, ready and willing,  to lend my expertise to this little enterprise of yours. It looks like you're lacking a  $WorldObject_25$. If you get me settled, I'll show you what useful things I can bring into town for you.][UnlockObjectID:25]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Collection][Text:Oh ho ho! Thank you very much, This will look great on display!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Happy][Text:How lovely!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Pleased][Text:What a nice thought!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Neutral][Text:Hm, well thank you.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>13</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Sad][Text:Hm... might be better to sell this one.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>14</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Miserable][Text:I can't even imagine anyone would want to buy something like that.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>15</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Ulm][Text:That $Actor_43$ sure is something, isn't she? I heard that someone asked her for a discount once and then...
Well, let's just say it hasn't happened again.][Villager:43]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
