<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Hm? Oh! Hi! I didn't expect to see anyone out here.
...
You're looking for me, are you? Heh... Well I guess I've been taking my time after all and got a bit distracted. Sorry about that!
It's nice to meet you! I'm $Actor_7$, Wandmaker by trade.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:1][Text:I hear you're an artisan right? That sounds so much more interesting than what I do. Do you enjoy it?][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:2][Text:Hey, $Name$. You ever have one of those days where you just feel like you can't do anything right? Yeah. Hope your day is going better at least.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh, hello $Name$, What can I do for you?][Name:ShopOpen]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:What? I haven't done anything to deserve this. Thank you.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Selection][Text:Hey.][Selection:VillageTalk]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Maintenance][Text:What do you want to do?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Collection][Text:This is!? No. how did you get this? I don't... I can't...
Really?
Thank you so much!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Raining|1][Text:My mother used to tell me stories of monsters that came out when it was raining. I know she just made them up but, sometimes, I can't help but wonder, you know?][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_Start][Text:Wait, before we go could I get you to lend me a hand? I was looking for some $Item_227$. It's a type of plant with some minor magical properties and very useful for making rods. If you could look for a few for me, that'd be very helpful.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_End][Text:You found some? Marvelous! This will keep me stocked for a few days at least.

Town was this way you said? I'll see you there!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_16_Start][Text:Not what I'd call a town, but it's a lovely start. Could I bother you to build a little something for me? I need to place to work and relax you understand.][UnlockObjectID:22]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
