<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Well hello there! The name's $NPC_11$. Merchant by trade, and I'm ready to get to work. If we're going to accomplish anything here, we're going to need a shop. First though, you had better talk to $NPC_14$. He says we need a $WorldObject_40$ before we can do anything else.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hello! You know, my family has been living in this town for over a century. It may not look like much, but this town runs in my blood.][Default][Name:1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Lovely day today, isn't it? It's a wonder what some fresh air will do for you!][Default][Name:2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Name:ShopOpen][Text:Oh, hello $Name$, What can I do for you?][Selection:Shop]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:Thank you!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Selection][Text:Well now, what can I do for you?][Selection:VillageTalk]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Raining|1][Text:What are you doing running around today? On a day like this, you should be inside where it's warm and dry.][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Raining|2][Text:My father used to tell me stories about nature spirits when I was a lad. Apparently some of them like to play in the rain. I fancy I can sometimes hear one, but I've never seen one with my own eyes.][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_Start][Text:So, I've been thinking...
With the store all set up, we've got some goods available and that's great, but that's just the start. We can't stop there, oh no.
Merchants often wander the roads, buying and selling goods and there is a fortune to be made from them! By setting up a $WorldObject_108$, we'll give them a place to display their wares and sell them ours.
Never forget, commerce is the lifeblood of a town, my friend. It might not seem like it now, but we'll need a lot of money if we're to grow this town.][UnlockObjectID:108]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_End][Text:The $WorldObject_73$ is finished? Excellent job, I can't wait to see what all the Merchants will bring.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_2_Start][Text:Ah! Good to see you again, I see that you've got the $WorldObject_40$ up and running so now it's time to set up that shop. You just set one up for me, and I'll see to it that we can start getting in supplies.][UnlockObjectID:26]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_2_End][Text:Great job! If you come back tomorrow, I think I'll have some more work for you to do.]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
