<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Hey. $Name$ right? Glad you made it. I'm $Actor_16$, and I'm here to help you with building the town.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:1][Text:Hey there, $Name$, hope you're feeling well today!][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:2][Text:Hey, $Name$, you make your way into the woods today? I'm always looking to get my hands on more wood.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Name:ShopOpen][Text:Oh, hello $Name$, What can I do for you?][Selection:Shop]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:Wow! Thanks!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Selection][Text:Hey.][Selection:VillageTalk]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_0_Start][Text:We have to build a $WorldObject_112$ so that visiting merchants will have a place to trade goods. You'll need wooden planks and some clay to build it.
	  I've got some extra planks in the chest there, but you'll need to find the clay yourself. I think I saw a cave in the woods where you that should be able to find some. Just follow the cleared path to the West.
	  Once you've got that, choose a spot, set it up, and let me know when you're done, OK?][UnlockObjectID:112]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_0_End][Text:Is the $WorldObject_112$ finished? Great! The Merchant's Guild knows we're here, so there should be someone along soon but that leaves the little problem of us not having anything to sell  yet.
...
So, before we left, I reached out to my colleagues to see what would be a good idea to start with. They suggested an Apothecary might be useful, adventurers always need potions and ointments.
An Apothecary was supposed to have arrived today, to get us moving in that regardbut she hasn't arrived yet.
 Could you check the woods again for me?
 Oh, and before I forget, here's a chest for you to hold items in. Place it anywhere you want, and take a look through these notes when you have a minute.][Face:Happy]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_6_Start][Text:NEED MORE PEOPLE]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_6_End][Text:BIG TOWN!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_18_Start][Text:While you're out, could you make sure to get as much lumber as you can? We're going to need a lot of wood for building.
Forty planks sounds like a good start, so just place twenty lumber in the bin by the door and I'll whip them up overnight!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_18_End][Text:We're off to a great start!][Money:50]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Collection][Text:This is just what I've been looking for!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>13</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Happy][Text:This is great, thanks!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>14</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Pleased][Text:Thanks a lot!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>15</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Neutral][Text:Oh, uh. Thanks.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>16</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Sad][Text:That's ok, I'd rather not.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>17</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Miserable][Text:Why would you think I'd like this?]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
