<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Thanks for the hand, I've been trapped here for a week and let me tell you I am sick of it. You got a camp around here somewhere?
	  A town you say? Well, that sounds like a much better sight than these walls. I'll meet you there after I pack.][SendToTown]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Slow Down][Text:How come all the rush all the time? You need to slow down and relax.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Anvil Smash][Text:Y'know, it's hard to be stressed when your job involves pounding an anvil all day. Couldn't recommend it more.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:Oh, thank you. I really appreciate this.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Collection][Text:Is that really for me? $Name$! Thank you. This really means a lot to me.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Selection][Text:Hello, what can I do for you?][Selection:VillageTalk]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:JoinPartyYes][Text:Certainly, I'd like to see what we can accomplish.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:JoinPartyNo][Text:Sorry,I'm very busy today. Maybe in a few days I can go with you again.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Yes I will marry you!][Name:MarriageYes]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:MarriageNo][Text:Oh... I'm sorry but. No.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Raining|1][Text:You're running around in this rain? Ha, of course you are. There's no stopping you, is there? It's admirable, if concerning.][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_3_Start][Text:Cheery little place here, and the drink ain't bad either! Now that you're here though, let's get down to brass tacks.
I've been looking for a new place to settle down, has some... unpleasantness back home. I was going to head down to one of the big cities like Easthem, but since you help me out I think maybe I'll stay here.
I'm more likely to make a mark in a small village like this anyway! What do I need I hear you ask? Simple! Nothing more than setting up a $WorldObject_35$ for me.][UnlockObjectID:35]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Testing][Text:Panda][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
