<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Hello there. My name is $Actor_26$ and I'm.. honestly not exactly sure how I got here..? 
This is such a nice little village, isn't it?
Although... where is here exactly?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:1][Text:Hello dear, having a good day?][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:When I was younger, young men and women from all over would come through here. Adventurers and gloryseekers, looking to make names for themselves. I can see the same fire in you.][Default][Name:2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh, hello $Name$, What can I do for you?][Name:ShopOpen]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Wow! Thanks!][Name:Gift]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hey.][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Maintenance][Text:What do you want to do?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh look at you, all soaked. Alex, you know you shouldn't go out when it's raining. Go sit by the fire and I'll bring you some stew.][Weather:Raining][Name:Raining|1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Raining|2][Text:The sound of the rain is pretty isn't it? It always makes me think of when I was younger. My family used to settle in on those rainy nights around the fireplace and tell each other stories. I hope Jesse comes home soon.][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Snowing|1][Text:... hm? Oh, hello dear. I was lost in my thoughts. It's alovely day out, isn't it? My husband and I used to go out for walks on days like this.][Weather:Snowing]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Name][Text]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_Start][Text:Yes?
...
Oh, you're looking for me? But I just got here... Oh, would you look at the time... I guess I did get a bit distracted. I'm $Actor_26$, it's delight to meet you.
I suppose I should be getting back to town, these old bones are getting rather tired. Is there any chance you could lend me a hand?
I was looking for some $Item_227$. It's a magical herb and very useful for making rods. If you could look for a few for me, that'd be very helpful.
I'll see you back at the $WorldObject_28$.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_End][Text:You found some? Delightful! This will keep me stocked up for a few days at least. Now, we just need to sort out my work space.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>13</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_16_Start][Text:Not quite what I'd call a town, but it's a lovely start. Could I bother you to build a little something for me? Once that's done, I can get to work.][UnlockObjectID:22]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
