<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Good to see you up and about! My name's $Actor_20$ and welcome to the Blue Hare Inn.
I know it looks a bit rough, but I think it's a good start yeah?
It won't be long until people start showing up.
I'll keep the visitors entertained as best I can, but you'll have to check in because I'm sure there'll be people flocking to move here in no time!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Hammer][Text:When $Actor_16$ and I were building the Inn, I hit my thumb at least three times with a hammer. I couldn't hold anything for days afterwards.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Clumsy][Text:I've always been kind of clumsy. Just one of those things, you know? My mother never gave me anything valuable to hold onto after the Incident with the pickle jar...]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Busy][Text:There's always things to do around here to keep me busy. Doubt you have it any better though, eh?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Scream][Text:I was just putting out the trash last night when I saw this... SHAPE rustling in the bushes.
I admit it, I screamed. I thought some horrible monster had crept down from the woods. Turns out it was just $Actor_43$ searching for $Item_100$.][Default][Villager:43]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Name:5][Text:You seem stressed, have you been making sure to get enough rest? A warrior is useless without sleep.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Happy][Text:Are you sure? Thanks!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Collection][Text:Oh I.. I can't... how did you know? Thank you!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Selection][Text:Hello, what can I do for you?][Selection:VillageTalk]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_15_End][Text:That's amazing! Thanks, a lot.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Name:ShopOpen][Text:Hey][Selection:Shop]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Name:MarriageNo][Text:Oh... I'm sorry but. No.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>12</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Pleased][Text:Thank you, this is very thoughtful.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>14</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Neutral][Text:Oh. Thank you.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>15</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Sad][Text:Oh...  thanks.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>16</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift_Miserable][Text:...I appreciate the thought.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>17</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_17_Start][Text:Hey! How are things, settling in well? Good, good. Glad to hear it. Look, I was thinking... It might help convince people to move in if we thinned out the monsters a bit. I was going for a little stroll this morning and an $Actor_33$ popped out of the bushes!
I'm fine, only my dignity is hurt, but since you're the only one with a weapon here, maybe you could go out and encourage them to back off?
Thanks.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>18</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_17_End][Text:I can breathe a bit easier now thanks! Although I guess it won't be too long until we've got more of them to deal with...
Urgh, it makes my hands itch just thinking about it.]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
