<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Text:... Oh? Hello dear, it's so nice to see a friendly face. I've been traveling for some time, you see. I'm $NPC_21$ a traveling healer. I hate to be a bother, but is there any chance you could make room for me here? I think it's time for me to get some rest for the first time in a while.][UnlockBuildingID:65][Name:Introduction]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hello dear, having a good day?][Default][Name:1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:When I was younger, young men and women from all over would come through here. Adventurers and gloryseekers, looking to make names for themselves. I can see the same fire in you.][Default][Name:2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh, hello $Name$, What can I do for you?][Name:ShopOpen]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Wow! Thanks!][Name:Gift]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hey.][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Text:What do you want to do?][Name:Maintenance]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh look at you, all soaked. Alex, you know you shouldn't go out when it's raining. Go sit by the fire and I'll bring you some stew.][Weather:Raining][Name:Raining|1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Text:The sound of the rain is pretty isn't it? It always makes me think of when I was younger. My family used to settle in on those rainy nights around the fireplace and tell each other stories. I hope Jesse comes home soon.][Weather:Raining][Name:Raining|2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Text:... hm? Oh, hello dear. I was lost in my thoughts. It's alovely day out, isn't it? My husband and I used to go out for walks on days like this.][Weather:Snowing][Name:Snowing|1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Text:You know... now that I've settled in, I was thinking. This town could really use an $Building_24$. It's been so long since I've taught anyone. My Jesse would sit at my knees and listen to my tell him the names of all the plants and herbs...
If you could build me such a place, that would make an old woman very happy.][ShopTargetID:2][UnlockItemID:137][Once][Default][Priority:50][Name:Apothecary_Request]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
