<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:!
	  Come to finish the job, have ye? Alright then, Bigjob, come and get it!
	  ...
	  What's that? You're not a bandit? A village you say? Well now, that's convenient ain't it? Name's Ulm, and it'll be a pleasure to meet you once you do me a small favor.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hello dear, having a good day?][Default][Name:1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:When I was younger, young men and women from all over would come through here. Adventurers and gloryseekers, looking to make names for themselves. I can see the same fire in you.][Default][Name:2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh, hello $Name$, What can I do for you?][Name:ShopOpen]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Wow! Thanks!][Name:Gift]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hey.][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_Start][Text: Y'see, I twisted my ankle when I was scarpering from some thugs the other day. It would be real sweet of you to find me three $Item_432$, that should patch me up for now.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_1_End][Text:Is that $Item_162$ I smell?
Knew I could count on you, Bigjob. Now let me just... Ah! Much better. So I believe you said something about a town yes? I'll see you there, and we can talk business!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_2_Start][Text:You call this a town? More like a sad clump of buildings if you ask me...
	  Lucky for you, I am an expert Apothecary. You build me a nice little home to call my own, and I'll see to it that the merchants have more than enough potions and unguents to keep them coming.][UnlockObjectID:18]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
