<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[string, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>Introduction</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Um, hi! $Character_2$, I mean,my name is $Character_2$. It's nice to meet you. I heard that you've opened an $Building_24$?
I'd love to help out. I've been looking for a place to practice my skills, I'm still learning, you see...][UnlockBuildingID:14]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh, $Name$, it's nice to see you.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:$Name$, how are you? I... hope everything's alright with you.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Gift</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh? No, you shouldn't have. I mean, I'm grateful but... If you're sure.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Collection</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh! I've been wanting this! Thank you so much.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Selection</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hey, $Name$, what do you need?{{Talk-Talk|Gift-GiveGift|%Friend-50%Join Party-Party|Never Mind-Cancel}}]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>JoinPartyYes</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Are you sure? I guess I can join you for an adventure today.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>JoinPartyNo</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Sorry... I've got things to do today. Maybe later?]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>MarriageYes</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Yes I will marry you!]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>MarriageNo</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Oh... I'm sorry but... No.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Raining|1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I don't like the rain. It's depressing.][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Raining|2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I'm glad to see you today, $Name$. You should try to dry off though. Those wet clothes can't be good for you. ... I mean, you should get home and dry off as soon as you can! That's all.][Weather:Raining]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Snowing|1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:It's nice, isn't it? The snow I mean? I uh, hope you've dressed warm.][Weather:Snowing]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Snowing|2</Key>
      <Value>[Text:$Name$... uh, how's the weather? I mean. How are you finding it? Not too cold I hope?][Weather:Snowing]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Fran_1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Did you see $Character_4$ last night? She seemed to be in a bad mood, I thought I saw her hex a squirrel...
I better not get on her bad side.][Villager:4]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Damien_1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I heard $Character_8$ singing at the $Building_7$ last night. He's really good, isn't he? I wonder if he'd teach me...][Villager:8]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Griselda_1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I had to stop by the $Building_8$ earlier for some reagents... I was looking around and accidentally knocked over a whole jar or herbs!
I ran before she caught up to me... I hope she's not too mad. I should go apologize.][Villager:17]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Emmanuel_1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:$Character_3$ is pretty funny isn't he? He asked me if I could do anything about a grey hair he found.
I didn't know what to say so I just suggested he pluck it? He didn't seem to like my suggestion.][Villager:3]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Ander_1</Key>
      <Value>[Text:$Character_7$ seems nice, but he's always got this weird look on his face when I see him. I wonder what's wrong with him?][Villager:7]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
