<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Introduction][Text:Ah! There it is, you found my orb didn't you? I have been searching for it for some time now, and to think it brings me back here...
I've gotten ahead of myself though. Greetings, I am $Actor_10$ and I would repay you for finding my orb.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Gift][Text:For me? Oh, $Name$, you shouldn't have.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>[Name:ShopOpen][Text:Greetings.]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Greeeeeeeetings... ][Selection:VillageTalk][Name:Selection]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>4</Key>
      <Value>[Text:I hope you can help me. Some upstart goblins snuck into my house last night and stole my orb. It's very precious to me, and I want it back. If you get it for me, I'll make it worth your while.][Name:Quest0]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>5</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Ah! You've arrived.
An artisan yes? I've never had the patience for that kind of thing. No, I prefer to wield my magic more directly. It's a useful skill though, one I'm glad you're bringing to the town.
Here. It's not much, just a few odds and ends I had laying around but it should get you started.][Name:Quest0End]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>6</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Dialogue|1][Text:Hm. Do you need something from me? It seems that people only want to talk to me when they need something. Out with it.][Default]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>7</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Hmm. You're in a rush today, aren't you? Slow down. The faster you run to your fate, the harder it is to escape the consequences.][Default][Name:Dialogue|2]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>8</Key>
      <Value>[Text:Huh, are you out and about today in this weather? In can't imagine why, it's intolerable. It's not fit for man, nor beast out there.][Weather:Raining][Name:Rain|1]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>9</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Snow|1][Text:Hm, snowing outside is it? $Actor_18$ loves the snow, but I can't stand it. I'll leave trudging through the snow to you younger ones and stay inside, thank you very much.][Weather:Snowing]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>10</Key>
      <Value>[Name:Task_11_Start][Text:I require a home with the right magical energies, you understand. I won't be able to do much living out of a hovel. This is what you'll need in order to meet my requirements.
I'll meet you when you're done, I have much to meditate on.][UnlockObjectID:31]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>11</Key>
      <Value>[Name][Text][Once][RequiredBuildingID:13][SendMessage:1]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
