<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[int, List[string]]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>
        <Item>[1:$1$... I wish you'd listen to me. You push yourself too hard.]</Item>
        <Item>[2:No. No I don't. I've told you before, I need to train. I need to be as ready as I can.]</Item>
        <Item>[3:Ready for what? I know you're skilled with that sword of yours, but every time you leave the house with it, I'm so afraid.]</Item>
        <Item>[4:So what? You'd rather I just cower in fear the next time monsters raid the town? No, I won't do that.]</Item>
        <Item>[5:..\nWe'll talk about this later, we have a guest. Is that you $Name$? I'm sorry you had to see that. What can I help you with?]</Item>
      </Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>
        <Item>[IntroText:The road has been your companion for days. Stretching on endlessely as you leave your old life behind, searching for a place that could use someone of your talents. All around you, you leave behind the remnants of a war-torn land, until at last you arrive here. A small valley, all but hidden from the last war. River Hollow.]</Item>
        <Item>[1:Well, this is it! I know it's not much to look at but I do hope you'll find it serviceable. It was a fine old house back in the day, but the years haven't exactly been kind to it.
Once the old owners left, we had our own problems keeping us too busy to maintain it. But I've had $Character_13$ take a look around inside and he assures me that it's safe, it just needs some love.]</Item>
        <Item>[2:...]</Item>
        <Item>[3:You said you're an artisan right? The old owners used to dabble in that sort of thing, it's how they made their money. There's some old equipment in the basement and $Character_17$ says she has some supplies for you. When you have a moment, you should go see her at her shop in town.
That should be enough to get you started, but you're going to need more supplies, so you should definitely explore the area.]</Item>
        <Item>[4:The field here is on the Eastern edge of the valley. To the North of here, across the field, there is an old shrine to the Great Spirit of the fields. $Character_20$ used to tell stories about the spirits and how people would pray at the shrines, but it's been a long time since anyone did that.]</Item>
        <Item>[5:To the West,just past the town, is the Forest, it's probably the best place for you to start if you're looking for reagents.
If you do go exploring, please be careful. You look capable, but it wouldn't do to have our newest resident sent to the apothecary on their first few days in the area now would it.
If you do find yourself needing any extra hands, $Character_16$, at the Adventurer's Guild will be able to help you.
Take care!]</Item>
        <Item>[6:]</Item>
        <Item>[7:]</Item>
      </Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>
        <Item>[IntroText:Something about the old harp calls to you. Idly, you strum your fingers along the strings, and a soft series of notes echoes throughthe long deserted Manor.]</Item>
        <Item>[1:...]</Item>
        <Item>[2:Is that... the harp?]</Item>
        <Item>[3:You! You've come home! Master! Oh, I had begun to think this day would never come. The Manor has a master again at last! I'm $Name$,the spirit of the manor, and it is my utmost pleasure to have one of your line to serve once more!]</Item>
      </Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>
        <Item>[1:Oh, hello $Name$. Sorry, I didn't see you there, lost in my thoughts... It happens, you know, when you get old. You have so much time in the past and some days all you can do is stop and think about what you've done...]</Item>
        <Item>[2:...]</Item>
        <Item>[3:I've been here, in River Hollow, for years now. I came during the war, seeking refuge and the kind people of the town opened their hearts to me.]</Item>
        <Item>[4:Long ago, back during the great war, I was a court mage for a nobleman whose name is now thought to be synonymous with cruelty. He was a good man once, or so I thought. The war though, it began to change him, twist him. It was as if some inner demon was driving him onwards, always seeking more power... more land. In his name I did many things, too terrible to mention. But one day, he asked the unthinkable of me.]</Item>
        <Item>[5:Knowing that refusal would result in imprisonment, I fled. In the middle of the night, I set my workshop ablaze and ran, never looking back.]</Item>
      </Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
