<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[string, string]">
    <Item>
      <Key>Introduction</Key>
      <Value>Eek! Eh... hello! New house person, yes? Me $0$. Place things here with me, yes, I sell for you at night while you sleeps. Mutually beneficial! [Talk:Talk|Gift:GiveGift|Ship Goods:ShipGoods|Never Mind:Cancel]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>Me going okies today. Bin is comfy, air is fresh. Very happies today</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>His mistake, probably, had been trusting the online Yelp reviews for the home inspector he’d hired during the negotiations. The website for Spengler Inspections had boasted glowing praise from happy customers, along with a professional-looking design and clearly stated rates and services. One of Dean’s pet peeves was when businesses refused to provide a price tag until you’d committed to signing on the dotted line, so the last factor alone had been a huge one. When Harry Spengler himself had shown up to do the inspection, Dean had realized he was dealing with a one-man shop. Not a deal-breaker, but the first of a cascading series of disconcerting revelations that had peaked with Spengler’s shifty request for a cash payment instead of a check.
Really, Dean should definitely have known something was wrong when the whole inspection was over and done in twenty minutes.
Electricity was something Dean knew well. He could map circuit boards in his sleep. Hell, he’d actually done that and more, often rousing from exhausted stupors as a grad student to find his bed covered in scrap paper and messy pencil scratchings of schematics he had no recollection of having drawn. Tracking down a problem circuit now should have been a matter of minutes, even considering that he was navigating by the flashlight on his camera to avoid starting fires from any other badly wired lights before he handled this one.
Locating the breaker box in the dark basement would have been an extra challenge if he hadn’t already noted, with mild curiosity, how the box was almost hidden completely behind a stubby brick wall segment that inexplicably jutted inward from the foundation wall. It almost looked as though the builder had been going for a shower stall, especially considering the mystery pipes bolted onto the brick and attached to nothing else, but that would make no logical sense. Who builds a shower around an electrical breaker?</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Gift</Key>
      <Value>Oh! Oh! Thank! Thank you very muchlike. This makes Shipping Gremlin very happy!</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Selection</Key>
      <Value>Hello, hello! How can meek, humble $21$ be helping you? [Talk:Talk|Gift:GiveGift|Ship Goods:ShipGoods|Never Mind:Cancel]</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Goodbye</Key>
      <Value>Okie Bye!</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
