<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[string, string]">
    <!--Key:NPCType#, Value:Text-->
    <Item>
      <Key>Introduction</Key>
      <Value>Hi! I'm $0$, it's good to see a new face around here!</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>Hey there, $^$,hope you're feeling well today!</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>Arthur knew from the moment the dark haired boy appeared before him, that there was something about him. Perhaps it was the insults he so easily slung without any intent of apology. Perhaps it was his thin and small frame that looked so easily breakable. Or maybe it was the way his eyes shone with emotion and something else. Something mysterious. Nevertheless, he annoyed Arthur and so he put the lad in the stocks. It was overly easy, being Prince. Arthur didn't expect to next see the boy in the palace, serving at the feast. Arthur had thought he was just passing through, or else visiting a family member inside Camelot, not becoming a servant in the palace. Arthur wasn't sure if he liked this or not. Still, he watched the boy carefully, trying to find out what it was about him. He smirked when the boy began noticing and seemed to squirm in place as if he could escape Arthur's gaze. But he wasn't so tame, even though it was clear he was doing his best to behave here. It was clear in the gaze he lifted to meet the Prince's, eyes a hard glare with his lips drawn into a frown that made them look so delicious. So bitable. It didn't take long for his suspicions to grow, after all, he had what he would call an intellectual fascination with magic. Not that he would ever dare admit it to anyone. Especially the fact that as a boy, Arthur had attempted to learn the ways of magic. He had failed though, and instead took to studying all he could of sorcerers and witches. He watched each execution, each prisoner, each found guilty with the utmost care, always going back to how he had seen them before they were caught, blending in with the people. Arthur had found that there was something about magic users in the way they stood, walked, or even looked. Something that held both power and fear. In some cases anger, but it was a way to tell of when they had something to hide, and Arthur made sure to learn it well. And the boy, Merlin, seemed very much like he was hiding magic. Well, at the very least he was hiding something. So Arthur decided to pull out all his hidden books and scrolls on sorcery. He went through them during his spare moments. However, something unexpected came to pass. Merlin had saved his life, and as a result, was appointed to be Arthur's manservant. He could see the clear dismay on the boy's face when his father, King Uther said it. Arthur matched the dismay, not liking having the boy thrust upon him, intruding upon his research. He had a manservant, a decent one that he had clear rules to abide by. Normally it wouldn't be too difficult to 'train' a new manservant into abiding by Arthur's strict rules, but Merlin.. Arthur knew Merlin wouldn't be so easily commanded. Hey, $^$, you don't happen to need any new weapons, do you? I've got a few at the shop that I think could come in handy.</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Gift</Key>
      <Value>Oh wow, really? Thanks $^$!</Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>Selection</Key>
      <Value>Hey, what's up?.[Talk:Talk|Gift:GiveGift|%Friend:50%Join Party:Party|Never Mind:Nothing]</Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>