<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<XnaContent xmlns:Generic="System.Collections.Generic">
  <Asset Type="Dictionary[string, List[string]]">
    <Item>
      <Key>0</Key>
      <Value>
        <Item>[1:$1$... I wish you'd listen to me. You push yourself too hard.]</Item>
        <Item>[2:No. No I don't. I've told you before, I need to train. I need to be as ready as I can.]</Item>
        <Item>[3:Ready for what? I know you're skilled with that sword of yours, but every time you leave the house with it, I'm so afraid.]</Item>
        <Item>[4:So what? You'd rather I just cower in fear the next time monsters raid the town? No, I won't do that.]</Item>
        <Item>[5:..\nWe'll talk about this later, we have a guest. Is that you $^$? I'm sorry you had to see that. What can I help you with?]</Item>
      </Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>1</Key>
      <Value>
        <Item>[IntroText:A long time ago, a great war broke out between the three kingdoms. Many lives were lost and as a result, much knowledge and hope was lost in the land. There is one place, however, where the spark of hope still burns, although the fires are quite low. That place, is River Hollow.]</Item>
        <Item>[1:Well... Heh, this is it. It's not much to look at I'm afraid.]</Item>
        <Item>[2:...]</Item>
        <Item>[3:I'm told it was once a fine old house, but after your grandparents passed... we just weren't really able to maintain it.]</Item>
        <Item>[4:You should take the time to explore the manor. Maybe you'll find something useful that's still usable. Good luck, I hope to see you around town soon.]</Item>
      </Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>2</Key>
      <Value>
        <Item>[IntroText:Something about the old harp calls to you. Idly, you strum your fingers along the strings, and a soft series of notes echoes throughthe long deserted Manor.]</Item>
        <Item>[1:...]</Item>
        <Item>[2:Is that... the harp?]</Item>
        <Item>[3:You! You've come home! Master! Oh, I had begun to think this day would never come. The Manor has a master again at last! I'm $^$,the spirit of the manor, and it is my utmost pleasure to have one of your line to serve once more!]</Item>
      </Value>
    </Item>
    <Item>
      <Key>3</Key>
      <Value>
        <Item>[1:Oh, hello $^$. Sorry, I didn't see you there, lost in my thoughts... It happens, you know, when you get old. You have so much time in the past and some days all you can do is stop and think about what you've done...]</Item>
        <Item>[2:...]</Item>
        <Item>[3:I've been here, in River Hollow, for years now. I came during the war, seeking refuge and the kind people of the town opened their hearts to me.]</Item>
        <Item>[4:Long ago, back during the great war, I was a court mage for a nobleman whose name is now thought to be synonymous with cruelty. He was a good man once, or so I thought. The war though, it began to change him, twist him. It was as if some inner demon was driving him onwards, always seeking more power... more land. In his name I did many things, too terrible to mention. But one day, he asked the unthinkable of me.]</Item>
        <Item>[5:Knowing that refusal would result in imprisonment, I fled. In the middle of the night, I set my workshop ablaze and ran, never looking back.]</Item>
      </Value>
    </Item>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
